( woman screaming )
- No ! - ( blow lands )
( shouting ) Get me Agent Chester Desmond out in Fargo , North Dakota .
( children crying , screaming )
- ( phone rings ) - ( horn honks )
Jake . Come over here and help out .
The phone .
- ( phone rings ) - ( horn honks )
- Hello . - Chet ?
I 'm calling you from Portland , Oregon .
It 's Regional Bureau Chief Gordon Cole calling from Portland , Oregon .
Okay , Gordon .
( shouts ) Oregon !
- ( static squawking ) - A young girl has been murdered !
Seventeen years old !
Named Teresa Banks .
Chet , We got a surprise for you .
Something interesting I would like to show you .
Arrangements are being made ,
and I will meet you at the private Portland airport .
Okay , Gordon .
( crying , screaming continue )
Chet ! Good to see ya .
Gordon .
Chet , give Sam Stanley the glad hand .
He 's come over from Spokane .
Its a pleasure . I 've heard a lot about you .
Sam 's the man who cracked the Whitman case .
Congratulations .
( shouts ) I heard about that .
Chet , your surprise .
GORDON : Her name is Lil .
She 's my mothers sister 's girl .
Federal .
Good luck , Chet .
Sam , you stick with Chet .
He 's got his own M.O.
Modus operandi .
You fellas can reach me in the Philadelphia offices .
I 'm flying out today .
That really was something with the dancing girl , wasn 't it ?
What exactly did that mean ?
I 'll explain it to you .
Remember , Lil 's wearin ' a sour face .
What do you mean ?
Her face had a sour look on it .
We 're gonna have problems with the local authorities .
They 're not gonna be receptive to the FBI .
Both eyes blinkin ' means trouble higher up .
The eyes of the local authority .
Sheriff and a deputy 'd be my guess .
You noticed she had one hand in her pocket , which means they 're hidin ' somethin ' .
And the other hand made into a fist , which means they 're gonna be belligerent .
Lil was walkin ' in place ,
which means there 's gonna be a lot of legalwork involved .
Cole said Lil was his mother 's sister 's girl .
Now , what 's missing in that sentence ?
The uncle .
Not Cole 's uncle , but probably the sheriffs uncles in federal prison .
Let me ask you somethin ' , Stanley .
Did you notice anything about the dress ?
The dress was altered to fit her .
I noticed a different colored thread where the dress was taken in .
Gordon said you were good .
- The tailored dress is our code for drugs . - Oh .
You notice what was pinned to it ?
A blue rose ?
Good .
But I can 't tell you about that .
You can 't ?
No , I can 't .
Good afternoon .
Federal Bureau of Investigation .
Special Agent Chet Desmond .
Id like to see Sheriff Cable , please .
- ( scoffs , Snickers ) - ( snickers )
Why don 't you have a seat over there with your partner ?
Go ahead , make yourself at home , ' cause it 's gonna be a while .
( high-pitched laughing )
( whispering , snickering )
Why don 't you have some coffee ? Go ahead .
It was fresh about two days ago .
( laughing )
( whispering )
All right , We had enough of the waiting room now .
Oh , is that so ?
( groaning )
( groaning , muffled screaming )
You can start that fresh pot of coffee right now .
- How the hell did you get in here ? - Federal Bureau of Investigation .
Special Agent Chet Desmond .
I 'm here to investigate the murder of Teresa Banks .
Well , little fella ,
we don 't need any outside help around here .
I don 't like you people sniffin ' around my neck of the woods .
In fact , when the state boys called me about a J. Edgar comin ' up here ,
I think I said ...
" So What ? "
( groaning )
Its all right , Deputy .
Sheriff Cable can handle it from here .
Cliff .
Your behavior is not funny .
It 's wasting the time of the federal government .
You 're lucky I 'm not wastin ' you .
Well , little fella , let me put it this way .
The operative word here would be " Federal . "
I am now ordering you to release all pertinent information concerning Teresa Banks ,
both while living and deceased .
A basic kill .
Banks was a drifter and nobody knew her .
Wheres the body ?
It 's out in back in our morgue .
It 's 4 : 30 . We close at 5 : 00 .
We have our own clock . We 'll lock up .
You know , Agent Desmond ,
I figure this whole office , furniture included , is worth $ 27,000 .
( sliding )
Teresa Banks .
Teresa Banks lived at the Fat Trout Trailer Park for a month .
We 'll check that .
Yeah .
Worked as a waitress at Hap 's Diner .
Worked the night shift .
Good place for dinner when were through here , Sam .
Yes .
No one came to claim the body .
No known next of kin .
( Clicks )
Crushed skull .
Probable cause , repeated blows to the back of the head
by a blunt , obtuse , angled object .
I wonder where her ring is .
Personal effects include a watch ,
undergarment , pink waitress uniform .
The rings missing .
Seems to be an interesting contusion ...
under the ring finger of the left hand .
Accidental ?
- ( creaking ) - ( grunts )
( clicking )
Agent Desmond ?
Could you hold the finger for me , please ?
There 's something in there .
SAM ( grunts ) : Yes .
What is it ?
It 's a piece of white paper ...
with the letter " T " imprinted on it .
Come here . Take a look .
Agent Desmond , ifs 3 : 30 in the morning .
Where are we going to sleep ?
We 're not . You and I are gonna get some food .
- Ask Irene about that . - ( electricity crackling )
Irene out there .
Now , Irene is her name , and it is night .
Don 't go any further with it . There 's nothing good about it .
- Thank you , Jack . - ( crackling continues )
How 's it goin ' with that goddamn lamp ?
( crackling continues )
Federal Bureau of Investigation .
Special Agent Chet Desmond .
Id like to ask you a few questions about Teresa Banks .
Jack said you knew her .
How well ?
She only worked here a month .
Nice girl .
Never seemed to get here on time though .
You ask me , she had a little problem with ...
( sniffing )
Did you ever see Teresa Banks take cocaine ?
No .
Do you ever take cocaine , Irene ?
No , I do not .
I never took cocaine or any other drug .
I don 't take drugs .
Nicotine 's a drug . Caffeine 's a drug .
Who 's the towhead ?
Those drugs are legal .
He 's with me .
Is there anything you 'd like to tell us about Teresa Banks that might help us out ?
I been thinkin ' about that .
You ask me ,
her death
was what you 'd call ...
a freak accident .
Thanks .
Are you talking about that little girl that got murdered ?
You got somethin ' to tell us ?
I know shit from Shinola .
La nuit est le bon moment .
Agent Desmond .
Do you think we should question him ?
What time is it , Stanley ?
( groaning )
It 's late , Sam .
It 's late , man . I 'm s - Hey , take it - I 'm sorry .
It 's early . It 's really early .
You know , I ... I never told anybody this ,
but once , for about three days ,
just before her time ,
Teresa 's arm went completely dead .
What do you mean ?
Her left arm .
It was numb .
She said she couldn 't use it .
Probably those drugs she was taking .
I just thought I oughta tell you .
Thanks .
Are you talking about that little girl that got murdered ?
I doubt it was a drug problem .
It was probably a nerve problem .
I could recheck the arm for injuries , but ...
I 'd have to take the body back to Portland to do some real nerve work .
I think that 's a good idea , Sam .
Irene .
We 'd like to order some food , please .
You wanna hear about our specials ?
We don 't have any .
- ( rooster crowing ) - ( car doors open , close )
MAN ( shouting ) : What ?
What is it ? What ?
- 9 : 00 . - 9 : 00 .
- MAN : Can 't you read ? - It 's really late .
- Or really early . - Damn .
This better be important .
Federal Bureau of Investigation . Special Agent Chet Desmond , Agent Sam Stanley .
I 'm sorry to disturb you , but we need to see Teresa Banks ' trailer , please .
Oh , shit .
That goddamn trailer is more popular than Uncle 's Day in a whorehouse .
You see what I mean ?
It just means , I - More shit I gotta do now .
Damn it .
Everythings exactly like she left it .
I haven 't touched a goddamn thing .
God .
Take a look at this .
SAM : She 's got the ring on .
Well , I 'm gonna make myself a cup of Good Morning , America .
- Y 'all want some ? - CHET : Yes , please .
- Here you go , boys . - Hey .
- Good Morning , America . - Thanks .
Thank you .
- ( coughing ) - ( clears throat )
You weren 't kidding , man . This stuff 's got the sting of the 48-hour blend .
( laughs ) That 's right .
That 's the best goddamn coffee you 're gonna get anywhere , buddy .
We sure do need a good wake-me-up , don 't we , Agent Desmond ?
- Yeah , we do , Sam . - ( both laughing )
Mmm .
Did you know Teresa Banks ?
( shallow breathing )
( electronic beeping , warbling )
( stammers )
See , I-I 've already gone places .
I-I ... I ju -
I just wanna stay where I am .
( wind gusting through trees )
What the hell 's that thing doin ' out there ?
You 're not takin ' that body anywhere .
We 're takin ' the body back to Portland .
There 's not a thing you can do about it .
Teresa Banks had a ring .
Any idea what happened to it ?
We got a phone here .
Its got a little ring .
( snickering )
Take the van back to Portland , Stanley .
I 'm gonna take one more look at the trailer park .
Agent Desmond ?
One thing has been troubling me .
The blue rose .
You 're going back to the trailer park for the blue rose .
That 's Deputy Cliff 's trailer right there by that red truck .
That 's his truck too .
And Teresa Banks ' trailer is over ... over here ?
Right where we left it .
Wheres my goddamn hot water ?
See what I mean ?
( clears throat ) I 'll be in my trailer .
- Hot water , Carl . - I 'm gonna get you some Valium , Margaret .
( electronic beeping , warbling )
Gordon , ifs 10 : 10 a.m. on February 16 .
I was worried about today because of the dream I told you about .
( bell dings )
Gordon !
DALE : Gordon !
( shouting ) Phillip ? is that you ?
Phillip ?
GORDON ( shouting ) : Cooper , meet the long-lost Phillip Jeffries .
You may have heard of him from the Academy .
Well , now .
I 'm not gonna talk about Judy .
In fact , we 're not gonna talk about Judy at all .
- We 're gonna keep her out of it . - Gordon .
( shouting ) I know , Coop .
Who do you think this is there ?
Suffered some bumps on the old noggin ' , eh , Phil ?
( shouting ) What the hell did he say there , Albert ?
That 's Special Agent Dale Cooper .
For God 's sakes , Jeffries , where the hell have you been ?
- ( loud , inorganic roaring ) - GORDON : You 've been gone damned near two years .
JEFFRIES : I sure as hell wanna tell you everything .
But I haven 't got a whole lot to go on .
( voice : backward effect )
JEFFRIES : Oh , believe me , I followed !
JEFFRIES : It was a dream .
We live inside a dream .
( voice : backward effect )
JEFFRIES : Ring .
The ring .
It ' was above a convenience store .
( voice : backward effect )
JEFFRIES : Listen up , and listen carefully .
I 've been to one of their meetings .
Hell , God , baby , damn , no !
I found somethin ' !
And then there they were .
( screaming )
GORDON : He 's gone ! He 's gone !
Albert , call the front desk !
I 've got the front desk now . He was never here .
And news from Deer Meadow .
Agent Chester Desmond has disappeared .
DALE : Gordon , whats going on ?
He was here .
But where did he go ?
And where is Chester Desmond ?
That 's her trailer over there , and I never touched a goddamn thing .
Agent Chet Desmond come by a second time
and asked to see Deputy Cliff Howard 's trailer over here ,
which I showed him .
Then I went back to my trailer
and after that never saw him again .
Thank you , Carl . Sorry to wake you .
It 's all right .
I was havin ' a bad dream anyway .
That 's not the way out to Deputy Cliff 's trailer . I told you .
I 'm not going to Deputy Cliff 's trailer .
Well , where the hell are you going ?
I 'm going over here .
Whats over there ?
Goddamn , these people are confusing .
What are you looking for ?
What was here , Mr. Rodd ?
A trailer was here . What the hell do you think ?
Can you tell me whose trailer it was and who stayed in it ?
Uh , an old woman and her grandson .
Can you tell me what their names were ?
Chalfont .
As a matter of fact ,
Chalfont was the name of the people that rented this space before .
Two Chalfonts .
Weird , huh ?
Is that Agent Desmond 's vehicle ?
Yep . Sure is .
DALE : Diane , it 's 4 : 20 p.m.
I 'm standing here at Wind River
near the location where the body of Teresa Banks was found .
Diane , this case gives me a strange feeling .
Not only has Special Agent Chester Desmond disappeared without a trace ,
but this is one of Cole 's blue rose cases .
The clues that were found by Special Agent Desmond and Agent Stanley
have led to dead ends .
The letter that was extracted from beneath the fingernail of Teresa Banks
gives me the feeling that the killer will strike again .
But like the song goes ,
" Who knows where or when ? "
( Clicks )
Donna !
Just a minute , Laura .
Hi .
Yeah , Mike , and yours the real man .
That 's right . Mike is the man .
( both repeating ) Mike is the man .
Laura Palmer .
See you later .
Laura .
See you in a second .
( sniffs )
( school bell ringing )
( bell continues ringing )
( door opens )
Hey , baby .
( whispers ) Just kiss me .
It does matter .
We 're in love .
James , you don 't know what you 're talking about .
Quit tryin ' to hold on so tight .
I 'm gone .
Long gone .
Like a turkey in the corn .
You 're not a turkey .
A turkey is one of the dumbest birds on earth .
Gobble , gobble , gobble .
Don 't ever leave .
Laura , don 't ever leave .
I 'll never leave you .
- ( conversation , whispered ) - Hey !
Where were you for the last hour ? I 've been looking all over for you .
I was standing right behind you ,
but yours too dumb to turn around .
If he turned around , he might get dizzy and fall down .
Where were you ? I 'm not kiddin ' around .
Who were you with ?
Get lost , Bobby .
Oh , yeah ?
You 'll be callin ' soon and maybe I won 't be around .
Come on , Bobby .
Come on .
Just a little one .
Good .
I love you , babe .
MAN : ♪ Like the night my girl went away ♪
♪ Gone off in a world filled with stuff ♪
♪ Lights start changing And there 's wires in the air ♪
♪ And the asphalt ♪ Man !
♪ It 's all around me ♪
♪ And I look down ♪
J ' And my shoes J '
♪ Are so far away from me ♪
♪ Man , I can 't believe it ♪
♪ I got a real indication ♪
♪ Of a laugh coming on ♪
Are you gonna see James tonight ?
Why are you suddenly so interested in who I 'm gonna see at night ?
Night time is my time .
You 're telling me .
That 's only because you won 't let me in on any of it .
You 're not gonna see Bobby , are you ?
Maybe .
My God , Laura .
Well , why not ?
Because Bobby is a loser . You said so yourself .
He 's a goon .
James is the one .
He loves you with that everlasting love .
True love .
Yes , James is very sweet .
Why don 't you get out your violin , Donna ?
" Sweet " ?
God , he 's gorgeous .
Yes , James is very sweet ...
and very gorgeous .
I wonder if Mike could ever write a poem .
( laughing )
Do you think that if you were falling in space ...
that you would slow down after a while or go faster and faster ?
Faster and faster .
And for a long time you wouldn 't feel anything .
And then you 'd burst into fire .
Forever .
And the angels wouldn 't help you .
Because they 've all gone away .
Mom ?
MAN : ♪ So I 'm going down this street ♪
♪ And I 'm tryin ' not to smile ♪
♪ ' Cause this street is where I 'm going ♪
♪ And the curb is at the side ♪
♪ By the sewer ♪
♪ Where the rain goes down ♪
♪ Like this girl I once knew ♪
♪ ' Cause the sewers are so hollow ♪
( shouts ) ♪ And the yell ♪
♪ ♪ ( horns imitating yell )
♪ Could last forever ♪
♪ Like the night my girl went away ♪
♪ Gone off in a world filled with stuff ♪
( ripping sound )
♪ Lights start changing And there 's wires in the air ♪
♪ And the asphalt ♪ Man !
♪ It 's all around me ♪
( ripping sound )
♪ And I look down ♪
♪ And my shoes ♪
♪ Are so far away from me ♪
♪ Man , I can 't believe it ♪
♪ I got a real indication ♪
♪ ♪ ( music stops )
( tires screeching )
- ( knocking ) - Mm-hmm .
Laura ?
My secret diary .
There are pages missing .
Who would do that ?
Bob .
But Bob is not real .
There are pages torn out ! That is real , Harold !
Well , maybe . Maybe .
Okay .
Bob is real .
He 's been having me since I was 12 .
And the diary was hidden too well .
There is no other person who could 've known where it was .
He comes in through my window at night .
He 's real .
He 's getting to know me now .
He speaks to me .
What does Bob say ?
He says he wants to be me , or he 'll kill me .
Oh , no .
- No . - Yes !
Yes !
What ? What ? Please , what ?
Fire ...
walk ...
with me .
Me !
( screams , sobbing )
The trees . The trees .
You have to hide the diary , Harold .
You made me write it all down .
He doesn 't know about you .
You 'll be safe .
I 'm sorry .
( sobs )
Laura .
What ?
I don 't know when I can come back .
Maybe never .
Laura !
( fan thrumming )
BOB : I want to taste ...
through your mouth .
No .
Lately I 've been filled with the knowledge that the killer will strike again .
But because it is just a feeling , I am powerless to stop it .
One more thing , Albert .
When the next murder happens , you will help me solve it .
Let 's test it for the record .
Will the next victim be a man or a woman ?
A woman .
All right .
What color hair will she have ?
Blonde .
Tell me some other things about her .
She 's in high school .
She is sexually active .
She 's using drugs .
She 's crying out for help .
Well , damn , Cooper , that really narrows it down .
You 're talkin ' about half the high school girls in America !
Whats she doin ' right now ?
She 's preparing a great abundance of food .
Okay , here 's your change . Thank you .
Heidi 's got a bloody nose .
Bloody nose ?
Do you think you could give Laura a hand with Meals on Wheels ?
Um , I-I was just - I was busy . I was doing this .
You 're not that busy .
( bell tolling )
( man murmuring , faint )
( murmuring , faint )
This would look nice on your wall .
( whispering )
- Shelly ! - Yeah ?
Um , I-I-I can 't do the Meals on Wheels today .
I-I just - I just can 't .
What ?
( thrumming )
( clicking )
( hinge creaking )
( screams )
( screaming )
( sobbing )
( gasping , panting )
( sobbing continues )
( door opens )
Oh , my God ! Oh , my God !
No , no , no , no , no , no , no !
- ( car door opens , closes ) - ( engine starts )
No . No . No .
No ! No . ( sobbing )
No , its not him .
No . No , its not him ! Its not !
Its not him ! Its not him !
No .
- ( sobbing ) - Laura .
Donna , are you ...
are you my ... are you my best friend ?
Of course .
What is it , Laura ?
What 's wrong ?
I 'm your friend always .
Come on .
Hi , honey .
How 's Donna ?
Fine .
School ?
School 's fine .
Sit down .
Are you hungry ?
Not really .
Hmm .
You didn 't wash your hands before you sat down to dinner , did you ?
Hmm ?
Let me see .
Dad .
Oh , these hands are filthy .
Look .
There 's dirt way under this fingernail .
( footsteps )
- Leland , what are you doing ? - Look at this finger here .
- Leland . - Laura did not wash her hands before dinner .
- Oh , look at this . - Don 't .
Oh .
Is it from a lover ?
Did you get this from your lover ?
They don 't call them lovers in high school , Leland .
Bobby didn 't give you this .
How do you know that Bobby didn 't give her that ?
Did Bobby give you this ?
Or is there someone new ?
Leland .
Leave her alone . Don 't do that . She doesn 't like that .
- How do you know what she likes ? - Stop it !
Stop it !
You sit down and we 'll all have dinner .
Oh , I 'll sit down .
But not a one of us is going to start eating until Laura washes her hands .
Wash your hands !
( sobbing quietly )
( sobbing continues )
( sobbing )
What is it , Leland ?
( door opens )
Laura , honey ?
I love you .
I love you so much .
Dad .
Good night , princess .
( door closes )
Is it true ?
( snaps )
( loud , ambient roaring )
( roaring stops )
( voice : backward effect )
( hooting )
( hooting winds down , stops )
( clicking )
Don 't take the ring , Laura .
Don 't take the ring .
My name is Annie .
We been with Dale and Laura .
The good Dale is in the lodge and he can 't leave .
Write it in your diary .
( gasps )
( creaking )
( ambient rumbling )
( rumbling stops )
This is where we live , Shelly !
As if I didn 't know .
I 'm gonna show you how to wash this tile , and then you 're gonna do it .
- Come off it , Leo . I have to get ready for work . - What did you say ?
- Shelly , I 'm not fooling around anymore ! - ( whispers ) Okay .
The first thing you 're gonna learn is to have a good attitude !
That 's the key ! Anybody 'll tell you that .
- ( phone ringing ) - ( grunts ) Ow !
Don 't even think about going anywhere .
- I 'm not finished with you . - ( ringing continues )
- Yeah ? - Leo . Bobby .
What are you doin ' callin ' me here ?
I 'm sorry .
Um ... the footballs empty .
I 'm lookin ' for Santa Claus .
No way . You already owe me money .
5,000 , to be exact .
( mouths words )
Leo Johnson , are you telling me there 's no Santa Claus ?
( whispers ) Fuck .
( phone ringing )
Yeah , Roadhouse .
Jacques . Bobby .
I need some things , man .
( chuckles )
How come you only call me when you 're desperate , huh ?
You desperate , baby ?
Are you interested or not ?
Yeah , maybe , Bobby , baby .
Maybe . ( chuckles )
For 10K I have a friend who has what you want .
Oh , his stuff is the best .
Hit me .
Two days , midnight ,
near the sound of sawing wood .
( chuckles )
Jacques , you crazy fuckin ' Canadian .
This sounds big .
( knocking )
Laura ? Laura ?
Laura ?
Where are you going ?
Nowhere , fast .
And you 're not coming .
Laura , come on .
Remember me ? I 'm your best friend .
Laura .
Aren 't you gonna fix me a drink ?
Where are the cookies ?
You mean Fred and Ginger ?
Dancing .
If I had a nickel for every cigarette your mom smoked , Id be dead .
I 'll call you tomorrow .
Laura .
Laura !
( door opens )
( car door closes )
When this kind of fire starts ,
it is very hard to put out .
The tender boughs of innocence burn first .
And the wind rises .
And then ...
all goodness is in jeopardy .
( breathing shakily )
♪ Why did you go ? ♪
♪ Why did you ♪
♪ Turn ♪
♪ Away from me ♪
♪ When all the world ♪
♪ Seemed to sing ? ♪
♪ Why ♪
♪ Why did you go ? ♪
♪ Was it me ? ♪
♪ Was it you ? ♪
♪ Questions in a world ♪
♪ Of blue ♪
♪ How can a bear ? ♪
♪ That 's filled with love ♪
♪ Start to cry ♪
♪ When all the world ♪
♪ Seems so right ? ♪
♪ How ♪
♪ How can love die ? ♪
♪ Was it me ? ♪
♪ Was it you ? ♪
♪ Questions in a world ♪
♪ Of blue ♪
♪ When did the day ♪
♪ With all its lights ♪
♪ Turn into night ? ♪
♪ When all the world ♪
So , you wanna fuck the homecoming queen .
( chuckles )
Lets go around the world , babe .
♪ Why did you go ? ♪
This isn 't gonna get you to Walla Walla .
You do go all the way ,
don 't you , little girl ?
Sooner or later .
You willing to go all the way ? Huh ?
You gonna do it to me ?
( grunts )
Let 's boogie .
What the hell are you doing ?
You part of the deal ?
No , she isn 't .
- ♪ ♪ ( ends ) - ( applause )
What did you say your name was ?
Buck .
That was really nice , Buck .
- Yeah . - ( Buck laughing )
Okay , Donna .
Let 's go .
♪ ♪ ( loud instrumental blues rock )
( Laura , faint )
( faint )
( imitates gunshot )
( laughing )
Yeah !
( no audible dialogue )
( faint )
No !
Donna !
Get her out of here ! Get her out of here , Jacques !
Tommy .
Don 't ever wear my stuff !
Don 't ever wear my stuff , ever !
- I 'm sorry . - Jacques , help me get her home how !
Tommy !
I won 't wear your stuff .
Donna , not you !
♪ ♪ ( continues )
How did - How did I get in my house ?
How did I get in my bed ?
Life is full of mysteries , Donna .
Are you mad at me for wearing something of yours ?
I don 't want you to wear my stuff .
I do love you , Laura .
( sniffles )
I love you , Donna .
( crying )
But I don 't want you to be like me .
( Crying continues )
Why do you do it ?
Excuse me , honey .
We 're late to meet Mom for breakfast .
I 'll catch you later .
- Bye-bye , Donna . - Bye .
( door closes )
( hooting )
Dad , is the engine on fire ?
It smells like somethings burning .
( horn honking )
- Something is burning ! - Yes .
- It 's the engine . - You stole the corn !
I had it canned
- over the store ! - ( horn honking )
And , miss , the look on her face when it was opened !
There was a stillness .
- ( barking ) - Like the Formica table top !
The thread will be torn , Mr. Palmer !
- Come on ! - The thread will be torn !
( horn honking )
It 's him !
- It 's your father ! - ( shouting )
Stop it !
What was that about ?
- ( panting ) - Mister !
You shouldn 't do that to your engine .
You oughta take it easy , mister .
You 're gonna b-b-burn your engine out .
What the hell was all that about ?
Why doesn 't somebody do something about this ?
A man comes out of the blue like that ,
starts screaming at you like a crazy person
and , uh , harassing my daughter .
You all right , honey ?
- Dad , are you all right ? - Yeah .
LELAND : Teresa Banks .
You look just like my Laura .
So when 's the next business trip , big boy ?
Ah , soon .
And next time , let 's party with those girlfriends you told me about .
- Huh ? - Sure .
I can arrange that .
What are you doing ?
Who am I ?
I don 't know .
That 's right .
LAURA : Dad ?
Dad !
Who was that ?
He - He looked familiar . Have I met him ?
No , honey , you haven 't met him . Have you met him ' ?
No !
- Let 's go get your mother . - No , no .
Just-Just ... sit here for a moment .
- Oh , my God . - ( engine stops )
I mean , a man comes out of the blue like that . Whats the world coming to ?
( Laura gasps )
( no audible dialogue )
( gasps )
- Hey , handsome . - Hi .
- What 's wrong ? - Nothing .
Um , I chickened out .
( man , muttering )
Black dog runs at night .
You s-sure you 're okay ?
Yes .
Uh , wow .
Dad ?
Yes ?
Did you come home during the day last week ?
No .
Leave us alone !
Goddamn it ! Get back to your work !
I thought I saw you .
Oh , God . You know ...
I did stop home on Friday , come to think of it .
I had this severe headache .
And I was in the neighborhood , so I ...
darted in and out of the house to get some aspirin .
Where were you , Laura ?
I didn 't see you .
Um ,
I was just down the street .
( engine starts )
( no audible dialogue )
The same ring .
( low humming , static )
Who are you ?
Who are you really ?
- ( static hissing ) - ( faint hooting )
- ( screams ) - ( shouts )
( snorting )
( bell ringing )
Hey .
I 'm nearly out .
It 's taken care of , babe .
You and I are gonna make a big score tonight .
What is that ?
But this should tide you over .
Bobby .
Thanks .
A big score ?
Maybe our biggest .
Don 't tell Mike .
This is just between you and me .
Tonight .
Meet me two doors down from your place at 11 : 00 .
JACQUES : Midnight .
Near the sound of sawing wood .
♪ ♪ ( radio : pop , faint )
( laughing )
Do you love me , Laura ?
- Bobby . - Huh ?
Watch . Watch .
- ( laughing ) - Oh , that 's good , Laura .
That 's really good . You 're a great dancer .
BOBBY : Ooh .
( Laura laughing )
Choo-choo-choo-choo , choo-choo-choo-choo ,
choo-choo-choo-choo , choo-choo !
( Coughs )
Ooh .
Ooh !
( groans )
Come on , knock it off .
Knock it the fuck off !
( laughing hysterically )
- Give me the fuckin ' - - Okay , okay !
Give me the fuckin ' bottle .
Shut - Shh !
( laughing continues )
Baby ? I mean , Bobby .
I found a pine cone .
Shut up . Shh ! Shut up . Shut up .
- Bobby , I found some dirt ! - Shut up . Shut up .
Shut up .
- I found some dirt ! - Here he comes .
Here he comes .
Who sent you ?
Jacques .
That 's right .
- Wow ! - Oh !
You like that , little girl ? Huh ?
- What ? - ( Laura screams )
Aaah !
( grunts )
Oh , my God ! ( panting )
Oh , my God . Bobby , what did you do ?
Oh , fuck . I shot him .
Oh , my God ! ( panting )
I shot him . Fuck !
( gasps )
Get over here and help me !
Come here !
Fuck !
( snorts , laughs )
Shut the fuck up ! This isn 't funny , Laura !
This is not fuckin ' funny .
Now help me bury him .
Shit !
Bobby , you killed Mike .
This isn 't fuckin ' Mike !
Is this Mike ?
Bobby , do you realize what you did ?
You killed Mike .
Shut up .
( laughing )
Bobby .
Bobby , you killed Mike .
Just get fuckin ' - Shut the fuck up !
Shut the -
Come on . Lets get the fuck out of here .
- Come on ! - ( laughing continues )
Fuck ! Lets just get the fuck outta here .
Just get the fuck outta here . Come on .
Get that .
- Come on ! Get - - ( laughing hysterically )
Come on ! Get the fuck -
Fuck !
( horn honking )
Where were you last night ?
I thought we were supposed to get together .
( sighs )
You 're on somethin ' again , huh ?
James .
So , when will I get to see you ?
( door opens )
I gotta go .
( motor starts )
( sniffs )
( door opens )
( thrumming )
( grunts )
( growls quietly )
( growls )
( sighs )
( moaning )
( moans )
( whispering ) Who are you ?
Who are you ?
( moaning )
- ( grunting ) - Who are you ?
( grunting continues )
( screaming )
( screaming continues , echoes )
Laura , honey ?
I really would like to talk to you .
Laura , sweetheart .
- Laura . - No , no , no .
Laura , honey ?
Sweetheart ?
Laura , is something wrong this morning ?
( whispering ) Stay away from me .
( electronic warbling )
( static hisses )
No , not tonight .
Just give me some stuff to hold me over until tomorrow .
Why ?
Why not ? Where you goin ' ?
Where are you going ?
I 'm going home , Bobby .
( sobs )
You don 't want me .
You just want the blow , don 't you ?
Okay .
It 's okay .
Bobby 's got it .
( crying )
Good night .
Good night , sweetheart .
( sighs )
( phone rings )
Hello .
James .
Yeah , okay .
Oh , James ,
I do love you , but ...
Okay .
I 'll meet you in 15 min -
I 'll meet you in 15 minutes .
Okay ?
God , why did I say that ?
Fifteen minutes ?
( gasps )
( motorcycle revving )
( tires Screech )
( ceiling fan thrumming , faint )
( motor Off )
What the hell is wrong with you ?
That 's right .
There 's no place left to go , is there , James ?
What the hell 's that supposed to mean ?
You know it , and I know it .
Whats wrong with us ?
I mean , we have everything .
Everything but everything .
Laura .
( mocking ) Laura .
You always hurt the ones you love .
You mean the ones you pity .
Say whatever you want .
I know you love me .
And I love you .
I do love you , James .
Lets get lost together .
Shit !
What ?
He might try to kill you .
Laura .
( screams )
Whats wrong ?
What ?
If he finds out ...
Laura , whats the matter ?
Bobby killed a guy .
What are you talkin ' about ' ? Bobby didn 't kill anybody .
Do you wanna see ?
See what ?
Right .
Open your eyes , James .
You don 't even know me .
There are things about me ...
Even Donna doesn 't know me .
Your Laura disappeared .
Its just me now .
Laura .
What about this , James ?
I think you want to take me home now .
- Laura ! - ( crying ) Don 't !
Come on .
Don 't !
Just don 't ! ( crying )
I love you , James !
( revving motor )
You 're right on time , baby .
♪ ♪ ( instrumental blues rock )
Don 't .
Jacques ! Don 't .
Don 't tie me up tonight , goddamn it !
- Stop it ! - Don 't !
- Don 't ! - Laura !
My God ! Don 't tie me up , Jacques !
Don 't !
( grunts )
Leo , will you untie me ?
Leo , will you please untie me ?
Shut up !
Oh , my God . Oh , my God ! ( screaming )
( screaming )
( Leland screaming continues )
( Crying , screaming )
( screaming )
Daddy !
Bob ?
- Run ! Run ! - ( screaming )
( screaming continues )
Are you gonna kill me ?
Father .
If I die now , will you come and see me ?
( screaming )
Your diary .
I always thought you knew it was me .
Don 't look at me .
I never knew you knew it was me .
I want you .
I 'm so dirty . ( crying )
I 'm not ready .
I 'm sorry .
I 'm - I 'm sorry .
Let me in ! Let me in !
( Leland screaming )
Don 't make me do this !
No !
( screaming )
( grunting )
( voice : backward effect )
( roars )
( wind howling )
Judy .
♪ ♪ ( choir singing )
♪ ♪ ( choir continues )
♪ ♪ ( ends )